<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Programming on Programming Away</title><link>http://programmingaway.com/tags/programming/</link><description>Recent content in Programming on Programming Away</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 16:39:10 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://programmingaway.com/tags/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tic Tac Toe Challenge – Version 2</title><link>http://programmingaway.com/post/tictactoe-v2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 16:39:10 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://programmingaway.com/post/tictactoe-v2/</guid><description>Shortly after writing a Tic Tac Toe program in python for one of my programming challenges, I ran across a new Tic Tac Toe programming challenge from Robert Heaton. While looking through his challenge, I decided my program was too simple and needed to be updated with better written functions. The functions in my original Tic Tac Toe program were hardcoded in some ways and needed to be more abstracted.</description></item><item><title>Tic Tac Toe Challenge – Version 1</title><link>http://programmingaway.com/post/tictactoe-v1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:39:10 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://programmingaway.com/post/tictactoe-v1/</guid><description>In order to get better at programming, I decided to find programming challenges online and track how I solve them here. After a quick search on Duck Duck Go, I found a set of challenges at Ryan’s Tutorials. The first on the list is a Tic Tac Toe game which states:
Build a game of Tic Tac Toe. I would suggest you start off building a two player version then if you want a little extra challenge see if you can build a version where you get to challenge the computer.</description></item><item><title>Garage Door Controller</title><link>http://programmingaway.com/post/garage-door/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 16:39:10 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://programmingaway.com/post/garage-door/</guid><description>I have done many attempts to control my garage door with my phone over the years. I first attempted to control the garage door using sensors and relays and a Raspberry Pi. I loosely followed a guide for a project called IoT Gateway from a site called Low Power Lab. That introduced me to the programming language NodeJS. I learned a lot from this project, which involved programming, circuitry, and controlling the circuits from the program.</description></item></channel></rss>